[
    {
        "question": "1 + 1",
        "answer": "2",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "2 + 3",
        "answer": "5",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "4 + 4",
        "answer": "8",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "3 + 6",
        "answer": "9",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "7 + 2",
        "answer": "9",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "5 + 3",
        "answer": "8",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "9 + 1",
        "answer": "10",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "6 + 4",
        "answer": "10",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "8 + 2",
        "answer": "10",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "1 + 5",
        "answer": "6",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "2 + 2",
        "answer": "4",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "3 + 3",
        "answer": "6",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "4 + 6",
        "answer": "10",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "1 + 4",
        "answer": "5",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "5 + 1",
        "answer": "6",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "7 + 1",
        "answer": "8",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "1 + 7",
        "answer": "8",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "3 + 1",
        "answer": "4",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "2 + 6",
        "answer": "8",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "2 + 4",
        "answer": "6",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    }
]
